In this video, I'm going to show you how
you can run a profitable Facebook ads to
get web design clients for less than $4
for each leads as a web design clients.
And as you can see, these are my two top
performing ads. This has 17 leads for $4
each. And another one has 26
leads with $13 each. And I'm going to
switch off the the $13 one probably
tomorrow because I'm uh
creating lots of other ad creatives
which will perform better than this. And
I have I have some other for like 19
leads for $14, seven leads for $15,
which is
pretty good compared to how much you're
spending for a lead and how much you're
getting out of a client. Since we're
selling a website for free and we're
going to get clients for a monthly
recurring revenue, which is $97 to $297
to $497 every single month. In that
case, we are spending $4 for a client
who is going to pay us $100
every single month. If you take a
lifetime value, for example, let's say
our lifetime value of our client is just
1 year.
With that 1 year, you are getting
$1,200
for just $4 each. And I'm going to show
you the exact strategy and how you can
start getting leads for as cheap as
possible. At the time I'm recording this
video, the lead has
uh gone high for $4.50 and this morning
it was $3.50. So, it kind of fluctuates.
But anyway, uh I'm going to show you the
entire strategy on how it's done. For
example, we sell
free website to our uh local businesses.
And this is how I ended up turning my
free website offer into a paid offer.
For example, let's say
if it's a startup plan, a one-page
website, I'm going to give them a
one-page website totally for free and
sign them up for a $97 hosting fee. And
if they want anything else on top of it,
it's going to cost them 2,000 to 3,000
on a setup fee and 197, 297, or 497 in a
monthly recurring revenue.
And as you can see, all of the leads you
have seen, the 17 leads, 19 leads, or 26
leads,
uh not all leads are going to turn into
clients, but the client the leads who
turn into clients, they will be in a $97
price range if they don't want to move
ahead for the five-page website or
10-page website. But the clients who
need the five-page or 10-page, we will
get
uh the prices around 1,500, 3,000 to
9,000. So, these are not fixed price.
Some clients will bargain the price
uh to lower uh just a little bit. That's
why I went from 2,000 2,500 and 2,000 to
just 1,000. And now I'm going to quickly
show you how we build these free website
and why we are selling the free website
in the first place. And this is a
software called GoHighLevel. This is
where we build everything, and including
uh our monthly services, for example,
the reputation management, missed call
text back, uh email automation, SMS
automation, lead capturing system, uh
calendar booking, invoicing, everything.
Everything you think about selling as a
monthly service, we can provide with the
GoHighLevel. And now GoHighLevel has its
own AI studio, which can build website
with just prompts. And this is how I
build it uh ended up building all these
websites just with prompts. For example,
I'm going to quickly show you one of the
website,
uh which is a roofing website.
This is just a basic prompt and the
Google My Business page, and just with
the Google My Business page link, you
can build the entire website with the
client's information. And
these all the things you're seeing here
is functional. And all the information
you're seeing in the website is the
client's information, which is specified
in the Google My Business page. And the
call system is active, and everything is
functional, and all the images you're
seeing is built by AI. And this is just
a simple prompt, and which took 18
seconds to build these website. And once
This is just to show the website inside
the booking
the book to meeting. And once they're
happy with how the first looks,
the landing page looks, and we can start
building out the entire website just by
prompting more text. That's how easy it
is to build these website. And the
reason why we sell this for free is that
we're not making our main money
just with a setup fee. So, that's why we
are waiving the setup fee for the
one-page website and selling them for
free in exchange of the hosting fees,
which is going to be $97. And let's say
if you sold these website, which which
is barely taking you a minute, and
selling them to 10 different clients.
That's going to be $1,000 in monthly
recurring revenue. And trust me, selling
something for free, it always get more
leads compared to selling something for
let's say 1,000 to 5,000. And inside the
meeting, that's your job to convince
them to go with you and get the free
website to your clients, and sign them
up for a monthly recurring revenue from
97 to 297 to 497, or you can upsell them
for the five-page website or the 10-page
website for a 2,000 setup fee or a 3,000
setup fee. And if you want to access
this software and start building your
own agency and selling your services, I
will link that link a 30-day free trial
down in the description, so you can have
a trial and have a look at how
everything works, and then you can once
you start getting clients, you can start
paying to the Go High Level subscription
with your clients' money instead of your
own money. So, 30-day free trial, link
is in the description. And until last
month, I've just been doing cold
outreach. Yes, cold outreach still
works, and you can still get clients. As
you can see, these are
my coaching members who are still doing
the cold outreach and still getting
results. And yeah, 5,000,
1,000
on the first week, first client for 750,
5,000 in monthly recurring revenue,
1,000, 2,000, 800, 1,000. Like, you can
see that this is working for everyone,
including you. If you are brand new to
this web design game, and if you don't
want to waste time figuring out what
kind of strategy works and what doesn't
works, and if you want to get clients
just like these in few weeks of starting
your agency, just click the first link
in the description, and I can help you
out getting the same results you're
seeing
on the screen. Or if not, if you are
thinking about starting to running ads,
keep watching this video until the end.
I will show all the ins and outs on how
to get profitable
web design leads for less than $4 each
lead, which is going to turn into a
clients who are going to pay you
100 to 300 to 500 dollars every single
month.
First up, we're going to go inside the
Meta Ad Library. There are lots of
people who are running ads for their own
agency, and trust me, lots of people are
doing the free website offer itself. And
the main way to figure out what kind of
ads you are going to run, for example,
there are
different ways to run ads. You can run
static, you can run testimonial, you can
run before and after, you can run a
video ad. So the main way to figure out
what ad actually works and what doesn't
works is to go inside meta ad library
and we can snoop around what other
agencies are doing. And if you want to
find out the best performing ads, all
you have to do is go inside
facebook.com/ads/library
and here you select all countries and
select all [snorts] ads. And just search
for free website
um or if you don't want to run a free
website offer, just run
website.
And here you can find lots of people who
are selling the free website offer.
Let's say just click on one of the
agency.
Yeah, this is one of the agency who are
running the free website offer. They
have lots of video ads,
lots of image ads as you go as there you
see. And the best way to figure out
which ad is performing well is to always
have the active ads open. And here you
can see the date and time. So this ad is
started at 6 May and this ad is started
this yesterday and most of these ads are
launched yesterday. And you can just go
back and see all the other agency and
what they are doing.
And you can you shouldn't copy the
entire thing what they are doing. Just
get the inspiration and start creating
your own creatives and start testing
your own ads inside the meta ads you
have just created. So I'm going to show
you some examples of ad creatives. For
example, let's say static ads. So these
are the best way to show what kind of
services you're providing to your
clients. And again, these are the
examples I have took from the ads
library. I'm not going to show my actual
ads in this video. and if you want to
see the entire setup, I will make a
separate video on this topic next week.
So, you don't want to miss out, make
sure to subscribe. And yeah, this is the
best way. You are just putting it out
there. Uh showing everything.
Instead of giving the $5,000 or $5,000
pounds, we're building it for free and
you just have to pay the $79. So, this
is a similar kind of offer another
agency is doing.
Or you can just go full on graphic mode,
say free professional website and have
this
uh
uh reviews five star, five star. Even if
you don't have reviews, just put it out
there. Fake it until you make it. And
another way is to get more leads, which
I have seen, is to actually show your
face
to get more leads.
These graphics may look nice, but people
are not going to trust the graphics.
People are going to trust another
people.
And on the video style, it's again
showing the video and letting them know
why you are doing this for free. You
have to give a reason on these videos.
And this is the video
uh in this video, this guy will be
explaining we are doing this for free
and why we are doing this for free and
why you need to work with us. So, that's
this video's intention. And in this
video, everything is
targeted on the website itself. So, he
is saying, we're building free websites
and this is a have a look at the website
we just finished for our clients. And
just scroll through the the website on
the screen and show the results on the
screen. So, you can go with both
different ways. And the reason why I
have moved away from cold outreach is
that cold outreach is kind of getting
saturated. Everyone is doing the same
thing that people are watching on
YouTube. I'm a part of this problem. I
genuinely wanted to help you guys to get
more leads,
but the cold outreach stops working
because every single one is doing the
same script. Even they don't change
a single word. So, if a client is seeing
the same thing over and over again,
people are not going to trust. And
that's why you are not seeing these
kinds of results inside your own agency,
even if it's So, these guys are not
doing ads. And some of these guys are
not even doing cold calling. It's just
Facebook group outreach.
And yeah, I don't want to have my agency
stuck in this same spot
every single month.
And I have some friends in Bali who
suggested me to just give it a try
running ads.
And guess what? I'm seeing pretty good
results, and I'm getting
So, this is this morning. I saw this
morning. Each lead I was getting is just
three 3.58
dollars a lead,
which is I'm going to show you.
Yeah, as you can see, 17 leads for 14
dollars 14.54 54 dollars. And I am
working on lots of other
ad creatives, which will decrease the
leads
cost per results
even lower because I've been having
conversation with people who have been
running ads profitably for a long time.
And in Bali, there are people Everyone
is running
Facebook ads instead of doing cold
outreach. No one does cold outreach
anymore. And the people who you are
seeing on YouTube who are showing I'm
making 500,000 or 200,000 or 100,000 any
anywhere on that price point, even
10,000 or 20,000 that price point they
are not having enough time they will not
have enough time to do cold outreach
where it's
uh
it's it's a fluctuates. Maybe you have
you can get booked meetings today
you cannot have any booked meetings
tomorrow because you never know what
goes on. But when it comes to
running ads for your agency
you're putting this much money and
you're letting
Meta know that I need these
kind of clients for my agency and I'm
giving you this much money. And Facebook
is giving me
uh each lead for $4. So
technically I'm
paying Meta for
basically $5 for each client who are
going to pay me 100 the basic price
let's say 100 and not all of these leads
are going to convert into
uh
as a client but compared to doing the
cold outreach
uh where you may have five booked
meetings
three of them will show up and two of
them will show us interest and you end
up closing one client or none. So you
end up being in zero. But when it comes
to Facebook
ads people are coming to you. So it's a
inbound and the only reason you can get
more leads and more leads who can
convert into customers is that they know
you before you knowing them and they
actually trust you enough to give you
their name email and phone number and
you just give them a call book a meeting
and sell these websites. And guess what?
It's a free website. And you're running
ads for a free website. That's the only
reason that
uh
cost per lead it's so low less than $5.
You cannot see this kind of results in
any other
uh service area part of business. You
can only see these results if you're
selling something for free. And if you
Nothing in Nothing in life is for free.
You're just selling these website and
it's in exchange they're paying for the
hosting fees.
That's how simple it is
to run this business. And once you start
getting clients, you can put all the
money back straight back to the ad
spend. And if you increase the ad spend,
you can increase the leads which is
coming in and you can get more clients.
And this is what most of the YouTubers
you are seeing are doing. And as you can
see, I'm not showing my exact
ad creatives I'm personally using. As
you can see, I'm I'm going to blur this
anyway.
I have run 11 11 ads until now and
tomorrow I'm going to push another five
ads.
And the reason why I have switched off
all these ads because
I have a leads coming in 19 leads for 15
dollars
for each lead and seven leads another 15
dollars.
Which is not a huge blow. Yes, you're
paying 15 dollars to get a client who
can pay you 100 dollars each month.
So the lifetime value of each clients
outweighs the ad spend of let's say 15
dollars. But there's always a way you
can reduce the lead and I have been
testing this out for past two months and
this is the result of me not knowing
what I'm doing and I've wasted a lot of
money and I've wasted a lot of leads
which I couldn't know what to how to
convert them as a customer. But now I
have done all the
AB testing and I've spoken with all the
people who have been doing this for a
long time and that's the only reason I
have closed uh
more clients with a monthly recurring
revenue just the 97, 297, or 497 and
able to upsell these clients for 1,500,
3,000, and 1,000. And guess what? Each
website takes 5 minutes to build. That's
how simple it is.
You take some money, put it on the ads,
and the ad creatives is the most
important thing. No matter how much
money you're spending in each and every
ad campaign, if your ad creatives are
not good, people are not going to click
on it, and people are not going to
submit their information as becoming a
lead or becoming a customer. So, as I
mentioned before, I cannot show my
actual strategy and my actual ad
creatives here in YouTube uh for obvious
reason. I don't want to ruin my
business, but if you want a similar uh
setup for your ad campaign to get
each lead for around three $3 to $4 or
below $5 for each lead, you can click
the first
link in the description and book a
onboarding call, and I will only help
people who are actually willing to go
through with this business because I
don't want to waste my time if I feel
like you cannot get clients with my
help. And it's not just Facebook ads,
and if you do want to get ads with
organic outreach, I can do that as well,
but I can only help two people at a time
in a month period. So, if you want to
help, make sure to click the first link
in the description and book an
onboarding call, and if you want a free
trial of a 30-day free trial of
GoHighLevel, you can also get that link
and start building the websites and get
to know how to deliver the service and
how to set up the monthly recurring
revenue systems. For example, the
uh lead capturing system, uh automated
text messages, and call text back, SMS
and email automation,
SEO, reputation management, everything
you can do inside GoHighLevel including
building these website as a hook to lure
them in for our monthly recurring
revenue business model. I hope you got
some value sort of this video and I will
see you guys in the next video. Peace.